http://www.newyorkpops.org/policy

Skip to main content
privacy policy
privacy policyThis privacy notice discloses the privacy practices for newyorkpops.org. This privacy notice applies solely to information collected by this website. It will notify you of the following:
What personally identifiable information is collected from you through the website, how it is used and with whom it may be shared.
What choices are available to you regarding the use of your data.
The security procedures in place to protect the misuse of your information.
How you can correct any inaccuracies in the information.
Information Collection, Use, and Sharing We are the sole owners of the information collected on this site. We only have access to/collect information that you voluntarily give us via email or other direct contact from you. We will not sell or rent this information to anyone.
We will use your information to respond to you, regarding the reason you contacted us. We will not share your information with any third party outside of our organization, other than as necessary to fulfill your request.
Unless you ask us not to, we may contact you via email in the future to tell you about specials, new products or services, or changes to this privacy policy.
Your Access to and Control Over Information You may opt out of any future contacts from us at any time. You can do the following at any time by contacting us via the email address or phone number given on our website:
See what data we have about you, if any.
Change/correct any data we have about you.
Have us delete any data we have about you.
Express any concern you have about our use of your data.
Security We take precautions to protect your information. When you submit sensitive information via the website, your information is protected both online and offline.
Wherever we collect sensitive information (such as credit card data), that information is encrypted and transmitted to us in a secure way. You can verify this by looking for a lock icon in the address bar and looking for "https" at the beginning of the address of the Web page.
While we use encryption to protect sensitive information transmitted online, we also protect your information offline. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job (for example, billing or customer service) are granted access to personally identifiable information. The computers/servers in which we store personally identifiable information are kept in a secure environment.
Cookie PolicyLike many websites, The New York Pops collects cookies when you visit our website. Cookies are small text files that are stored on your computer or mobile device. Each cookie is unique to your web browser and contains anonymous information, like your IP address and what pages on our site you have visited, to help optimize your experience on our site. For example, we use cookies to make sure you do not receive a prompt to sign up for our mailing list if you have already entered your information or if you have declined the opportunity. The information we gather is not available to any third parties. If you would rather we do not use cookies when you visit our site, please configure your specific browser settings to reject cookies.
If you feel that we are not abiding by this privacy policy, you should contact us immediately via telephone at 212-765-7677 or via email at admin@nypops.org.
Buy Ticket: #
